Guide to the Vassar College Alumnae/i Biographical Files (AAVC), circa 1865-2015
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Class of 1894
  - Chater, Ellen D. (Box 9)
  - Clapp, Harriet B. (Box 9)
  - Coman, Caroline (Box 9)
  - Cooley, Grace W. (Box 9)
  - Corbin, Grace H. (Box 9)
  - Crampton, Susan c. (Box 9)
  - Crea, Mary Lillian (Box 9)
  - DeLaney, Josephine (Box 9)
  - Edwards, Grace (Box 9)
  - Elsworth, Ethel H. (Box 9)
  - Enos, Kate L. (Box 9)
  - Ferrell, Mary E. (Box 9)
  - Ferry, Blanche (Box 9)
  - Fisher, E. Grace (Box 9)
  - Fitch, Lucy A. (Box 9)
  - Fitch, Mary C. (Box 9)
  - Fowler, Charlotte L. (Box 9)
  - Fuller, Frances H. (Box 9)
  - Fuller, Zada Constance (Box 9)
  - Gallager, Elizabeth (Box 9)
  - Gillmer, Elizabeth A. (Box 9)
  - Gnade, Agnes (Box 9)
  - Golay, Juliette (Box 9)
  - Grimshaw, Blanche (Box 9)
  - Haight, Elizabeth H. (Box 9)
  - Hastings, Mabel L. (Box 9)
  - Hawes, Louise B. (Box 9)
  - Hemans, Ida M. (Box 9)
  - Hench, Lillie c. (Box 9)
  - Hendrickson, Mary H. (Box 9)
  - Holbrook, Myra C. (Box 9)
  - Howe, Leonora (Box 9)
  - Howell, Fanny Asenath (Box 9)
  - Hulbert, Edith J. (Box 9)
  - Hussey, Alice S. (Box 9)
  - Knaul, Cora D. (Box 9)
  - Latimer, Ada (Box 9)
  - Leonard, Clara Augusta (Box 9)
  - Lusk, Ida C. (Box 9)
  - Lynch, Mary (Box 9)
  - MacArthur, Florence (Box 9)
  - Macauley, A. Rachel (Box 9)
  - Macauley, M. Margaret (Box 9)
  - Marchant, Marie (Box 9)
  - Marshall, Elizabeth (Box 9)
  - May, Louisa S. (Box 9)
  - McAdams, Elisabeth M. (Box 9)
  - McCurdy, Caroline (Box 9)
  - McMorran, Emma J. (Box 9)
  - Miller, Louisa (Box 9)
  - Miracle, Kate Emily (Box 9)
  - Moore, Ethel (Box 9)
  - Mumford, Mary B. (Box 9)
  - Myers, Angie M. (Box 9)
  - Newman, Bessie P. (Box 9)
  - Patten, Elizabeth H. (Box 9)
  - Patterson, Lila H. (Box 9)
  - Platt, Emily B. (Box 9)
  - Pringle, Cornelia C. (Box 9)
  - Robbins, Florence L. (Box 9)
  - Simons, Lao Genevra (Box 9)
  - Slade, Helen M. (Box 9)
  - Spiers, Katharine (Box 9)
  - Stebbins, Katharine VanC. (Box 9)
  - Stickney, Ruth (Box 9)
  - Story, Ada (Box 9)
  - Thornton, Lucy R. (Box 9)
  - Todd, Flora E. (Box 9)
  - Tompkins, Nanna M. (Box 9)
  - Utter, Katharine M. (Box 9)
  - Vaillant, Abby A. (Box 9)
  - Van der Burgh, Carol (Box 9)
  - Van Kleeck, Melvina (Box 9)
  - Vaughan, Martha D. S. (Box 9)
  - Wagar, Harriet M. (Box 9)
  - Watt, Adelene K. (Box 9)
  - Wells, Emilie L. (Box 9)
  - White, Gertrude (Box 9)
  - Wilcox, Alice W. (Box 9)
  - Wilcox, Edith Field (Box 9)
- Class of 1895
  - Abbot, Etheldred (Box 9)
  - Abbott, Harriet E. (Box 9)
  - Acker, Margaret K. (Box 9)
  - Armstrong, Frances A. (Box 9)
  - Armstrong, Louise (Box 9)
  - Arnold, Katherine I. (Box 9)
  - Austin, Susie L. (Box 9)
  - Beard, Grace A. (Box 9)
  - Blodgett, Caroline E. (Box 9)
  - Boltwood, Elvira W. (Box 9)
  - Boyd, Elizabeth E. (Box 9)
  - Boynton, Georgie S. (Box 9)
  - Brendlinger, Margaret R. (Box 9)
  - Brinckerhoff, Anne (Box 9)
  - Brownell, Laura (Box 9)
  - Burnham, Pearl V. (Box 9)
  - Candee, Helen H. (Box 9)
  - Carpenter, Grace M. (Box 9)
  - Childs, May H. (Box 9)
  - Clark, Addie Laura (Box 9)
  - Cohen, France (Box 9)
  - Cookie, Carol (Box 9)
  - Crawford, Anne L. (Box 9)
  - DeLany, Emma T. (Box 9)
  - Dorrance, Anne (Box 9)
  - Doughty, Phebe V. (Box 9)
  - Durant, Bessie A. (Box 9)
  - Emery, Ethelyn (Box 9)
  - Estes, J. Agnes (Box 9)
  - Evans, Susan Hoyt (Box 9)
  - Fenton, Caroline L. (Box 9)
  - Fitch, Mary Goodrich (Box 9)
  - Fletcher, Hasseltine R. (Box 9)
  - Freeman, Florence E. (Box 9)
  - Garvin, Edith (Box 9)
  - Gedney, Mary Eleanor (Box 9)
  - Goodwin, Grace (Box 9)
  - Graham, A. Jeannette (Box 9)
  - Greer, Juliet (Box 9)
  - Gruening, Rose B. (Box 9)
  - Hasenwinkle, Elsie Barbara (Box 9)
  - Haughwout, Mary (Box 9)
  - Henry, Alice (Box 9)
  - Higgins, Edith Secor (Box 9)
  - Higman, Anna Clarissa (Box 9)
  - Hill, Clara M. (Box 9)
  - Hillier, Eddah (Box 9)
  - Hoagland, Susan W. (Box 9)
  - Holmes, Edith C. (Box 9)
  - Holmes, Harriet F. (Box 9)
  - Holmes, Helen M. (Box 9)
  - Howell, S. Edna (Box 9)
  - Hulst, Grace D. (Box 9)
  - Hutt, Elizabeth (Box 9)
  - Johnson, Alida L. (Box 9)
  - Johnson, Willie C. (Box 9)
  - Jones, Mabel I. (Box 9)
  - Kelly, Susan L. (Box 9)
  - Kircher, Otie (Box 9)
  - Ladue, Helen N. (Box 9)
  - Learned, Abbie F. (Box 9)
  - MacDonald, Jessie Lillian (Box 10)
  - MacVey, M. Louise (Box 10)
  - Marvin, Ellen S. (Box 10)
  - McCauley, Emma C. (Box 10)
  - McCutcheon, H. Louise (Box 10)
  - Merritt, Ethel A. (Box 10)
  - Mitchell, Merion E. (Box 10)
  - Monsch, Anna A. (Box 10)
  - Morgan, Bertha D. (Box 10)
  - Mulholland, M. Estelle (Box 10)
  - Mundy, Mary S. (Box 10)
  - Murray, Emma W. (Box 10)
  - Myers, Elsie (Box 10)
  - Nairn, Alice M. (Box 10)
  - Orvis, Julia S. (Box 10)
  - Orwig, Maud (Box 10)
  - Pelgram, Caroline M. (Box 10)
  - Phelps, Theodora A. (Box 10)
  - Pierce, Lucy Frances (Box 10)
  - Pinkham, Leila May (Box 10)
  - Poppenheim, Christie H. (Box 10)
  - Poppenheim, Ida H. (Box 10)
  - Potter, Marcia (Box 10)
  - Ramsdell, Helen E. (Box 10)
  - Reed, Mary M. (Box 10)
  - Reiley, Katharine C. (Box 10)
  - Reimer, Isabelle A. (Box 10)
  - Rugge, Alice E. (Box 10)
  - Sebring, Juliet (Box 10)
  - Simmons, Flora A. (Box 10)
  - Skelton, Jessie V. (Box 10)
  - Smith, Effie C. (Box 10)
  - Smith, Eleanor L. (Box 10)
  - Smith, Elizabeth C. (Box 10)
  - Smith, Frances A. (Box 10)
  - Snow, Ella G. (Box 10)
  - Snyder, Gabrielle M. (Box 10)
  - Strang, Bertha r. (Box 10)
  - Streeter, Mabel C. (Box 10)
  - Thorne, Elisabeth G. (Box 10)
  - Townsend, Wie D. (Box 10)
  - Turner, Julia E. (Box 10)
  - Twitchell, A. Mary (Box 10)
  - Updegraff, Elizabeth (Box 10)
  - Verhoeff, Mary (Box 10)
  - Vernon, Florence I. (Box 10)
  - Wagner, Mary S. (Box 10)
  - Watton, Maude C. (Box 10)
  - Weaver, Lillian C. (Box 10)
  - Welch, E. Marian (Box 10)
  - Williams, Edith (Box 10)
  - Witschief, Gertrude (Box 10)
  - Wood, Vinnie C. (Box 10)
  - Woodworth, Frances E. (Box 10)
  - Worthington, Alice L. (Box 10)
  - York, Frances T. (Box 10)
- Class of 1896
  - Adkins, Mary E. (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Bingley (Box 10)
  - Arnold, H. Winifred (Box 10)
  - Bainbridge, Helen Maud (Box 10)
  - Balance, Florence (Box 10)
  - Banks, Harriet S. (Box 10)
  - Barnes, Clara W. (Box 10)
  - Bayliss, Lilian (Box 10)
  - Beach, Laura J. (Box 10)
  - Bell, Jessie (Box 10)
  - Booker, Louise R. (Box 10)
  - Bowman, Ina C. (Box 10)
  - Branch, Laura M. (Box 10)
  - Brand, Nettie H. (Box 10)
  - Breckenridge, Mabel (Box 10)
  - Broad, Margaret (Box 10)
  - Brown, Margaret C. (Box 10)
  - Carbutt, Florence (Box 10)
  - Carrel, Theodora M. (Box 10)
  - Caswell, Mary Ursula (Box 10)
  - Chamberlain, Susanna W. (Box 10)
  - Champney, Marie (Box 10)
  - Chandler, Sarah Farquhar (Box 10)
  - Chesley, Gertrude L. (Box 10)
  - Childs, Annie S. (Box 10)
  - Collins, L. Frank (Box 10)
  - Coonley, Sarah O. (Box 10)
  - Cooper, Maude (Box 10)
  - Cornell, Clara M. (Box 10)
  - Cross, Lucile (Box 10)
  - Cumming, Ellen K. (Box 10)
  - Darrow, Elizabeth L. (Box 10)
  - Dance, Edith D. (Box 10)
  - Deane, Edith D. (Box 10)
  - Dewey, Gertrude A. H. (Box 10)
  - Dickinson, Tenny V. (Box 10)
  - Dillow, Pearl C. (Box 10)
  - Douglas, Anne E. (Box 10)
  - Dunham, Katherine S. (Box 10)
  - Edick, Grace Willard (Box 10)
  - Epler, Helen F. (Box 10)
  - Fagan, Josephine (Box 10)
  - Farrar, Annie Martha (Box 10)
  - Ferry, Queene (Box 10)
  - Freeman, Belle Margaret (Box 10)
  - Getchell, Helen (Box 10)
  - Grant, Blanche C. (Box 10)
  - Greer, Lily (Box 10)
  - Hagar, Alice P. (Box 10)
  - Hart, Jessie B. (Box 10)
  - Hartzell, Sarah B. (Box 10)
  - Bartlett, Mrs. Edwin O. (Box 10)
  - Hawkins, Caroline (Box 10)
  - Hayward, Ellen I. (Box 10)
  - Hewitt, Marie L. (Box 10)
  - Higgins, Mary E. (Box 10)
  - Higman, Nell (Box 10)
  - Hill, Helena C. (Box 10)
  - Hill, Julia D. (Box 10)
  - Howland, Alice M. (Box 10)
  - Hulst, Ella S. (Box 10)
  - Johnson, Mignonette B. (Box 10)
  - Jones, Blanche A. (Box 10)
  - Kinkead, Cornelia D. (Box 10)
  - Kruse, Ida G. (Box 10)
  - Laird, Marion (Box 10)
  - Lapham, A. Edith (Box 10)
  - Lawall, Marion L. (Box 10)
  - Lockhart, L. Marion (Box 10)
  - Love, Ella L. (Box 10)
  - Love, Emily (Box 10)
  - Mabie, Muriel K. (Box 10)
  - MacArthur, Gertrude E. (Box 10)
  - MacFarland, Maude M. (Box 10)
  - Madeira, Lucy (Box 10)
  - Maltman, Elizabeth E. (Box 10)
  - Mann, Ruth M. (Box 10)
  - Marquardt, Della M. (Box 10)
  - Martin, Carolyn G. (Box 10)
  - McAllester, Lillian A. (Box 10)
  - McCampbell, Roberta (Box 10)
  - McCloskey, Estelle (Box 10)
  - McClure, Mary L. (Box 10)
  - McKean, Ida P. (Box 10)
  - McMillan, Jeannette (Box 10)
  - Moore, Anne (Box 10)
  - Moore, Lillian R. (Box 10)
  - Morris, Anna R. (Box 10)
  - Morton, Anne (Box 10)
  - Newcomb, May Q. (Box 10)
  - O'Brien, Lucy D. (Box 10)
  - Paine, Elizabeth (Box 10)
  - Parkis, Alice Lackey (Box 10)
  - Parmele, Mary I. (Box 10)
  - Pettengill, Agnes Eliza (Box 10)
  - Phinney, Lulu A. (Box 10)
  - Reed, Bertha Lavinia (Box 10)
  - Reynolds, Kate B. (Box 10)
  - Richardson, Harriet (Box 10)
  - Richardson, Mary M. (Box 10)
  - Samson, Marian S. (Box 11)
  - Sanders, Mary N. (Box 11)
  - Scarborough, M. Douglass (Box 11)
  - Schwartz, Julia A. (Box 11)
  - Scott, Elizabeth G. (Box 11)
  - Scott, Florence B. (Box 11)
  - Scranton, Henriette (Box 11)
  - Sheppard, Louise P. (Box 11)
  - Sinsabaugh, Henrietta (Box 11)
  - Spalding, Sarah Griswold (Box 11)
  - Spencer, Mary D. (Box 11)
  - Stamford, Helen (Box 11)
  - Straight, Edith J. (Box 11)
  - Swift, Lulu (Box 11)
  - Tarbox, Mary E. (Box 11)
  - Throop, Katharine P. (Box 11)
  - Traver, Hope (Box 11)
  - Tryon, Geneva (Box 11)
  - Tunnicliff, Ruth (Box 11)
  - Tuttle, Alma E. (Box 11)
  - Van Anden, Louise (Box 11)
  - Wait, Olga D. (Box 11)
  - Walworth, Reubena (Box 11)
  - Warner, Maude L. (Box 11)
  - Wellington, Grace A. (Box 11)
  - Wellington, Marjorie S. (Box 11)
  - Welton, Mabel E. (Box 11)
  - West, Clara P. (Box 11)
  - Winkler, Rosalie (Box 11)
  - Winnington, Laura (Box 11)
  - Wood, Helen T. (Box 11)
  - Young, Bertha K. (Box 11)
- Class of 1897
  - Alexander, Laura V. (Box 11)
  - Anderson, Helen E. (Box 11)
  - Anderson, Mildred W. (Box 11)
  - Applegate, Katharine T. (Box 11)
  - Atkinson, Elisabeth B. (Box 11)
  - Baker, Emma L. (Box 11)
  - Baker, Mary Leonard (Box 11)
  - Baldwin, Elinor L. (Box 11)
  - Beard, H. Elizabeth (Box 11)
  - Beckwith, Frances A. (Box 11)
  - Benedict, Mary K. (Box 11)
  - Bemkopf, Flora B. (Box 11)
  - Bishop, Elizabeth L. (Box 11)
  - Bishop, Helen L. (Box 11)
  - Bishop, Sara Pancost (Box 11)
  - Bowman, Amy C. (Box 11)
  - Brigham, Mary H. (Box 11)
  - Brill, Emma C. (Box 11)
  - Brittain, Gertrude F. (Box 11)
  - Brown, Clara K. (Box 11)
  - Burchard, Anna T. (Box 11)
  - Burnet, Jean E. (Box 11)
  - Campbell, Blanche (Box 11)
  - Canning, Anetta Blanche (Box 11)
  - Capwell, Abby E. (Box 11)
  - Chambers, Mary E. (Box 11)
  - Chandler, Alice B. (Box 11)
  - Chapin, Marietta P. (Box 11)
  - Chase, Anne B. (Box 11)
  - Chesley, Mabel L. (Box 11)
  - Claflin, Adelaide (Box 11)
  - Clough, Gratia (Box 11)
  - Comstock, Harriet B. (Box 11)
  - Cook, Bertha (Box 11)
  - Craig, Evelyn N. (Box 11)
  - Crosby, Florence M. (Box 11)
  - Crane, Edith (Box 11)
  - DeGarmo, Mary Staats (Box 11)
  - DuBois, Nina Marjorie (Box 11)
  - Dudley, Sarah E. (Box 11)
  - Dunning, Mary G. (Box 11)
  - Easton, Alice F. (Box 11)
  - Ellery, Eloise (Box 11)
  - Ferrell, Nellie I. (Box 11)
  - Gallaher, Grace M. (Box 11)
  - Goodrich, Isabel F. (Box 11)
  - Granniss, Honoria E. (Box 11)
  - Greeley, Edith (Box 11)
  - Griffin, Maude V. (Box 11)
  - Guyer, Elizabeth (Box 11)
  - Hailey, Ellen Lake (Box 11)
  - Hardin, Caroline H. (Box 11)
  - Hartley, Grace (Box 11)
  - Hazeltine, Elizabeth H. (Box 11)
  - Heather, Celia Altah (Box 11)
  - Hecker, Mary M. (Box 11)
  - Hemmings, Anita F. (Box 11)
  - Heywood, Rose B. (Box 11)
  - Higgins, Medora L. (Box 11)
  - Higbie, Florence W. (Box 11)
  - Hommel, Lillian C. (Box 11)
  - Hooker, Emily G. (Box 11)
  - Hutchinson, K. Olive (Box 11)
  - James, Vassie (Box 11)
  - Kennedy, Lillian (Box 11)
  - Kirkland, Winifred M. (Box 11)
  - Landfield, Grace H. (Box 11)
  - Lapham, E. Marian (Box 11)
  - Lawrence, Irene (Box 11)
  - Leverett, Mary E. (Box 11)
  - Lewis, Hortense (Box 11)
  - Lord, Eliza M. (Box 11)
  - Lovejoy, Lillian (Box 11)
  - Mallon, Florence C. (Box 11)
  - McClelland, Nancy V. (Box 11)
  - McMahon, Mabel (Box 11)
  - McNair, Jean F. (Box 11)
  - Merrill, Mary (Box 11)
  - Meyers, Belah (Box 11)
  - Miersch, Ella E. (Box 11)
  - Neef, Harriet C. (Box 11)
  - Newell, Antoinette (Box 11)
  - Norris, Mabel (Box 11)
  - Peters, Helen E. (Box 11)
  - Phillips, Sara J. (Box 11)
  - Platt, Sara F. (Box 11)
  - Poe, Betty C. (Box 11)
  - Post, Anna W. (Box 11)
  - Raymond, Alice Scott (Box 11)
  - Reimer, Marie (Box 11)
  - Richey, Anna G. (Box 11)
  - Sarver, Martha Mevey (Box 11)
  - Sawyer, Alice W. (Box 11)
  - Schauffler, Rachel C. (Box 11)
  - Schibsby, Marian (Box 11)
  - Scofield, Julia A. (Box 11)
  - Shaw, Beatrice (Box 11)
  - Smith, Gertrude (Box 11)
  - Staton, Sally B. (Box 11)
  - Storke, A. Hermione (Box 11)
  - Straight, Grace C. (Box 11)
  - Sweet, Elizabeth M. (Box 11)
  - Taylor, Louise C. (Box 11)
  - Thain, Jessie I. (Box 11)
  - Thallon, Ida C. (Box 11)
  - Thornton, Emma C. (Box 11)
  - Traver, Madeleine M. (Box 11)
  - Tuttle, Clara M. (Box 11)
  - Tweedy, Grace B. (Box 11)
  - Verhoeff, Carolyn (Box 11)
  - Warner, Grace M. (Box 11)
  - Whitney, B. Belle (Box 11)
  - Whiton, Alice (Box 11)
  - Wilkinson, Annie L. (Box 11)
- Class of 1898
  - Ackerly, M. Belle (Box 12)
  - Adams, Isabel F. (Box 12)
  - Bagg, Marion C. (Box 12)
  - Ballance, Harriet N. (Box 12)
  - Bean, N. Keith (Box 12)
  - Belcher, Katharine F. (Box 12)
  - Belknap, Eleanor (Box 12)
  - Benway, Mabel R. (Box 12)
  - Black, Mary Louise (Box 12)
  - Blair, Esther Louise (Box 12)
  - Blanchard, Mabelle A. (Box 12)
  - Blunt, Katharine (Box 12)
  - Booth, Lydia R. (Box 12)
  - Borden, Fanny (Box 12)
  - Brink, Louise (Box 12)
  - Broad, Elizabeth (Box 12)
  - Bush, Elizabeth C. (Box 12)
  - Calhoun, Marian Harmon (Box 12)
  - Chamberlain, Louise A. (Box 12)
  - Clark, Anna W. (Box 12)
  - Cobb, Helen A. (Box 12)
  - Crosley, Bertha (Box 12)
  - Davis, Helen G. (Box 12)
  - Day, Anne M. (Box 12)
  - Deach, Mary Ama (Box 12)
  - DeLany, Mary E. (Box 12)
  - Dwight, Elizabeth D. (Box 12)
  - Eddy, Flora Ellen (Box 12)
  - Eddy, Lucretia G. (Box 12)
  - Evans, Florence Creagh (Box 12)
  - Ferris, Mabel R. (Box 12)
  - Forbes, May E. (Box 12)
  - Freeman, Nelly D. (Box 12)
  - Gardner, Julia G. (Box 12)
  - Garvin, Grace M. (Box 12)
  - Gibbons, Alice N. (Box 12)
  - Gibbons, Emma Culross (Box 12)
  - Gibbons, Ruby S. (Box 12)
  - Granger, May B. (Box 12)
  - Greenwood, Helen S. (Box 12)
  - Guernsey, Lydia R. (Box 12)
  - Haight, Helen I. (Box 12)
  - Hart, Fanny (Box 12)
  - Haskell, Katharine L. (Box 12)
  - Hastings, Blanche M. (Box 12)
  - Hartfield, Phebe A. (Box 12)
  - Haviland, Grace I. (Box 12)
  - Hemphill, Lucy B. (Box 12)
  - Hequembourg, Helen M. (Box 12)
  - Herbert, Clara Wells (Box 12)
  - Howard, Jessie B. (Box 12)
  - Howbert, A. May (Box 12)
  - Howe, Edna L. (Box 12)
  - Huddlestone, Mary E. (Box 12)
  - Jaques, Emily H. (Box 12)
  - Jarnagin, Martha S. (Box 12)
  - Jefferson, Dora E. (Box 12)
  - Johnson, Louise W. (Box 12)
  - Jones, Edith P. (Box 12)
  - Jones, Ella V. (Box 12)
  - Justice, Lucretia B. (Box 12)
  - Kauffman, Alice (Box 12)
  - Larrabee, Katharine P. (Box 12)
  - Lovell, Phebe D. (Box 12)
  - MacColl, Mary (Box 12)
  - Macfarlane, Alice C. (Box 12)
  - Mahan, Marie B. (Box 12)
  - Maltman, Grace I. (Box 12)
  - Marsh, Jane C. (Box 12)
  - Martin, Helen Edna (Box 12)
  - Maynard, Florence A. (Box 12)
  - McCall, Rosemary (Box 12)
  - McCarty, Maria C. (Box 12)
  - McCulloch, Roberta (Box 12)
  - McKay, Mabel (Box 12)
  - McKinney, Fanny L. (Box 12)
  - Merrick, Florence B. (Box 12)
  - Morey, Jeannette (Box 12)
  - Morgan, Mary H. (Box 12)
  - Morris, Sara H. (Box 12)
  - Mount, Helen E. (Box 12)
  - Mumford, Rosalie (Box 12)
  - Murdoch, Jane R. (Box 12)
  - Norton, Susan W. (Box 12)
  - Olivet, Florence W. (Box 12)
  - Paige, Mary Dresser (Box 12)
  - Parker, Alice B. (Box 12)
  - Potter, Louise E. (Box 12)
  - Reeves, Agnes W. (Box 12)
  - Rice, Laura O. (Box 12)
  - Riche, Julia (Box 12)
  - Robbins, Louise (Box 12)
  - Serviss, Ethel M. (Box 12)
  - Seymour, Bina (Box 12)
  - Shepard, Rachel Adelaide (Box 12)
  - Simpson, Elizabeth M. (Box 12)
  - Skinner, Helen Campbell (Box 12)
  - Sleight, Josephine W. (Box 12)
  - Smith, Alice H. (Box 12)
  - Smith, Nellie M. (Box 12)
  - Squires, Norma M`. (Box 12)
  - Stone, Agnes H. (Box 12)
  - Taber, Mary A. (Box 12)
  - Taylor, Florence E. (Box 12)
  - Trembor, Bertha A. (Box 12)
  - Valleau, Lillian M. (Box 12)
  - Vassar, Elizabeth F. (Box 12)
  - Voorhees, Grace L. (Box 12)
  - Ward, Edith G. (Box 12)
  - Warren, Mary Lee (Box 12)
  - Webster, Emma (Box 12)
  - Wentworth, Amy (Box 12)
  - Whitman, Helen L. (Box 12)
  - Wilkerson, Elizabeth B. (Box 12)
  - Young, Elizabeth A. (Box 12)
- Class of 1899
  - Abbott, Beatrice V. (Box 12)
  - Abbott, Caroline G. (Box 12)
  - Albro, Edna C. (Box 12)
  - Armsby, Maud (Box 12)
  - Baker, Eleanor R. (Box 12)
  - Batchelor, Rosa M. (Box 12)
  - Bates, Bertha (Box 12)
  - Belcher, Jane (Box 12)
  - Bidleman, Elinore R. (Box 12)
  - Blumenthal, Helen (Box 12)
  - Borden, Nannie J. (Box 12)
  - Bowman, Eda C. (Box 12)
  - Boyd, Katherine May (Box 12)
  - Boyd, Mary (Box 12)
  - Breed, Persis M. (Box 12)
  - Brown, Mabel Webster (Box 12)
  - Burnette, Jane (Box 12)
  - Burr, Marjorie (Box 12)
  - Burton, Claribel Daisy (Box 12)
  - Burwell, Elizabeth L. (Box 12)
  - Burwell, Ethel I. (Box 12)
  - Busey, Marietta R. (Box 12)
  - Chamberlin, Laura A. (Box 12)
  - Chandler, Una E. (Box 12)
  - Chase, Helen V. (Box 12)
  - Choate, Augusta (Box 12)
  - Clarke, Alice (Box 12)
  - Coles, Alice B. (Box 12)
  - Cook, Myra G. (Box 12)
  - Cotrael, E. Elisabeth (Box 12)
  - Creswell, Josephine (Box 12)
  - Crowell, Alice B. (Box 12)
  - Davis, Helen L. (Box 12)
  - DeFrees, Mary L. (Box 12)
  - DeLand, Minerva (Box 12)
  - DeLany, Eleanor A. (Box 12)
  - Dilatush, Carrie M. (Box 12)
  - Dransfield, Jane (Box 12)
  - Eastwood, Mary (Box 13)
  - Elting, Evarene (Box 13)
  - Evans, Mary R. (Box 13)
  - Field, Virginia (Box 13)
  - Fish, Alice P. (Box 13)
  - Fitzroy, Alexandria S. (Box 13)
  - Foster, Isabella G. (Box 13)
  - Fowler, Clarissa L. (Box 13)
  - Fry, Mabel L. (Box 13)
  - Fulton, M. Gertrude (Box 13)
  - Gardner, Mary E. (Box 13)
  - Garrett, Emma L. (Box 13)
  - Gathright, Margaret M. (Box 13)
  - Gildersleeve, Lillian (Box 13)
  - Grant, S. Georgiana (Box 13)
  - Greer, Florence (Box 13)
  - Hallaran, Mary (Box 13)
  - Hamburger, Stella (Box 13)
  - Hamilton, Jean (Box 13)
  - Harrison, Laurie H. (Box 13)
  - Hart, Louise S. (Box 13)
  - Hassler, Claire B. (Box 13)
  - Henry, Sarah Martha (Box 13)
  - Heywood, C. Gertrude (Box 13)
  - Hill, Edith (Box 13)
  - Hosmer, M. Louise (Box 13)
  - Hoy, Helen K. (Box 13)
  - Hoyt, Jean Boughton (Box 13)
  - Hurlbut, Mary E. (Box 13)
  - Ingersoll, Louise Mason (Box 13)
  - Isham, Susanna Hamlin (Box 13)
  - Jacobus, E. Louise (Box 13)
  - James, Jean E. (Box 13)
  - Jenkins, Ann Elizabeth (Box 13)
  - Jessup, Henrietta (Box 13)
  - Johnson, Clare L. (Box 13)
  - Johnson, Grace (Box 13)
  - Jones, Annie C. (Box 13)
  - Kelly, Agnes R. (Box 13)
  - Kennedy, Clara C. (Box 13)
  - King, Clara E. (Box 13)
  - King, Helen Edith (Box 13)
  - Kleberg, May L. (Box 13)
  - Lee, Agnes (Box 13)
  - Lehlbach, Anna (Box 13)
  - Loeb, Sara (Box 13)
  - Marshall, Florence M. (Box 13)
  - Martin, Blanche (Box 13)
  - Mathewson, Minnie D. (Box 13)
  - McCaffrey, Cora A. (Box 13)
  - Mears, Ruth B. (Box 13)
  - Merwin, Adele H. (Box 13)
  - Mesick, Irene L. (Box 13)
  - Miller, Alma M. (Box 13)
  - Miller, Susie G. (Box 13)
  - Moore, Edna Marion (Box 13)
  - Moore, Mary Agnes (Box 13)
  - Morrill, Grace (Box 13)
  - Moser, Regina V. (Box 13)
  - Murray, Margaret E. (Box 13)
  - Nessenson, Elsa B. (Box 13)
  - Nicols, Elsie (Box 13)
  - Noyes, Helen Maria (Box 13)
  - Otis, Susanna (Box 13)
  - Overmann, Marjorie (Box 13)
  - Davis, Mrs Norman H. (Box 13)
  - Patterson, Mabel L. (Box 13)
  - Percy, Ednah M. (Box 13)
  - Pettee, Julia (Box 13)
  - Philips, J. Tracy (Box 13)
  - Prichard, Lucy E. (Box 13)
  - Broenniman, Mrs. Eleanor R. (Box 13)
  - Richardson, Bertha (Box 13)
  - Robb, Sara Fox (Box 13)
  - Robbins, Grace H. (Box 13)
  - Roberts, Rosamond (Box 13)
  - Rockefeller, Lorinda R. (Box 13)
  - Rush, Edna Spaulding (Box 13)
  - Russell, Edith S. (Box 13)
  - Scofield, Harriet B. (Box 13)
  - Smith, Nathalie (Box 13)
  - Smith, Susan E. (Box 13)
  - Smurr, Bonnie (Box 13)
  - Spaulding, Leila C. (Box 13)
  - Spicer, M. Alberta (Box 13)
  - Sprague, Antoinette B. (Box 13)
  - Sprague, Florence E. (Box 13)
  - Stockholm, Helen W. (Box 13)
  - Stowell, Mary E. (Box 13)
  - Taggart, Alice R. (Box 13)
  - Thompson, Helen D. (Box 13)
  - Tompkins, Elizabeth M. (Box 13)
  - Toy, Grace Helen (Box 13)
  - Tozer, Alta M. (Box 13)
  - Travis, Florence C. (Box 13)
  - Truesdale, Phoebe K. (Box 13)
  - Turner, H. Velma (Box 13)
  - Tuttle, Anna S. (Box 13)
  - Updegraff, Rachel (Box 13)
  - Van de Warker, Mabel (Box 13)
  - Van Inwegen, Anna (Box 13)
  - Van Kleeck, Marie (Box 13)
  - Van Law, Maude Lucile (Box 13)
  - Van Syckel, Jean (Box 13)
  - Vanderslice, Isabel L. (Box 13)
  - Ware, Abby H. (Box 13)
  - Washburn, Katherine B. (Box 13)
  - Wheeler, Ruth (Box 13)
  - Wicker, Julia F. (Box 13)
  - Wilson, Anabel H. (Box 13)
  - Woodcock, Mary Louise (Box 13)
  - Wright, Julia H. (Box 13)
  - Yantis, Lola (Box 13)
- Class of 1900
  - Andrews, Grace (Box 13)
  - Angell, Josephine M. (Box 13)
  - Armstrong, Estelle R. (Box 13)
  - Barnard, Anna E. (Box 13)
  - Barnard, Violet (Box 13)
  - Barrows, Alice P. (Box 13)
  - Bartlett, Louise S. (Box 13)
  - Baxter, Katharine C. (Box 13)
  - Beadle, Phebe H. (Box 13)
  - Becker, Jessica M. (Box 13)
  - Beckwith, Florence M. (Box 13)
  - Belknap, Alice S. (Box 13)
  - Benedict, Marion M. (Box 13)
  - Birdsall, Agnes (Box 13)
  - Blakeslee, Sophie L. (Box 13)
  - Borden, Asenath (Box 13)
  - Bourne, Mary J (Box 13)
  - Bradley, Emma (Box 13)
  - Braun, Mabel (Box 13)
  - Brent, Marie L. (Box 13)
  - Brownell, Florence M. (Box 13)
  - Buckley, Laura (Box 13)
  - Budington, Anna (Box 13)
  - Budington, Margaret (Box 13)
  - Burnham, Alice M. (Box 13)
  - Byington, Grace Richmond (Box 13)
  - Campbell, Florence D. (Box 13)
  - Candler, Gertrude M. (Box 13)
  - Cann, Anna L. (Box 13)
  - Chapin, Ruth M. (Box 13)
  - Christopher, Lelia (Box 13)
  - Comstock, Marie B. (Box 13)
  - Corbin, Elizabeth B. (Box 13)
  - Corcilius, Irene (Box 13)
  - Cossar, Harriet B. (Box 13)
  - Crater, Annie M. (Box 13)
  - Dailey, Eva B. (Box 13)
  - Davis, Alice E. (Box 13)
  - Day, Pauline B. (Box 13)
  - Dean, Flora G. (Box 13)
  - DeGraff, Bessie L. (Box 13)
  - Denton, Julia (Box 13)
  - Dewey, Rusha A. H. (Box 13)
  - Dorrance, Frances (Box 13)
  - Dowling, Florence C. (Box 13)
  - Dubois, Eoline Church (Box 13)
  - Dunning, Margaret (Box 13)
  - Eiseman, Alice L. (Box 14)
  - Ellsworth, Caroline P. (Box 14)
  - Eshenour, Mary L. (Box 14)
  - Ess, Marion P. (Box 14)
  - Ettenson, Harriet E. (Box 14)
  - Fairhead, Lizbeth D. (Box 14)
  - Ford, Florence M. (Box 14)
  - Fowler, Leslie (Box 14)
  - French, Florence H. (Box 14)
  - Frothingham, Mary (Box 14)
  - Gallagher, Helen D. (Box 14)
  - Gaus, Daisy (Box 14)
  - Graham, Elizabeth (Box 14)
  - Greenhalge, Harriet N. (Box 14)